updatexp.com 2005-12-12

# www.updatexp.com Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

The following provides detail about the **www.updatexp.com** Privacy Policy.

**www.updatexp.com** , treats your privacy seriously. In general, I use the personal information that I collect from you to identify you and match your name against queries that you place with me.

**NOTICE:** This policy only applies to [ www.updatexp.com](http://www.updatexp.com/) services and not to the companies, individuals, organisations or other websites to which there are links.  
  
**1.** | **Consent**  
  | 

Your use of this web site signifies your consent to me collecting and using personal information about you as specified below in accordance with this Policy. Should  [www.updatexp.com](http://www.updatexp.com/) choose to change this Policy for any reason, the changes will be posted here, so that you are always kept informed of how www.updatexp.com collects and uses your personal information, and when I may disclose it.  
  
**2.** | **How Do I Collect Information About You and How Is It Used?**  
2.1 | You may provide personal information when communicating with [www.updatexp.com](http://www.updatexp.com/). For instance when you subscribe to our newsletter service or training emails.   
2.2 | 

You may order a product or a service and give your name, e-mail address, delivery address, credit or debit card number and expiry date so that the order can be processed and your products (or services where appropriate) delivered to you. Sometimes you may be asked for your telephone number.  
  
2.3 | If you enter a competition or promotion we will ask for your name, address and e-mail address.  
2.4 |  It may be that some of the personal information you give is sensitive personal data within the meaning of the Data Protection Act 1998 (UK).  Any such information ("sensitive information") will only be disclosed with your express consent.  
2.5 |  It may be that you provide to us details of credit or debit cards or bank accounts in order to make payments to us. Any such information ("confidential financial information") will be dealt with as described below.  
2.6 |  I may use personal information collected about you to personalise your visits to the web site and recommend goods or services to you. I also use the information to help me develop the design and layout of the web site to ensure that they are as useful and enjoyable as possible.  
2.7 |  I may use personal information collected about you to let you know about functionality changes to our web site or changes to our terms and conditions of use.  
2.8 |  **www.updatexp.com** will **NEVER** sell or give away the personal information collected about you to **ANY** 3rd parties.  
  |    
**3.** | **Traffic Data**  
3.1 | 

[www.updatexp.com](http://www.updatexp.com/) may provide aggregate statistics about our sales, customers, traffic patterns and other site information to third parties, but these statistics will **not** include **any** information that could personally identify **you**.  
  
**4.** | **Other Disclosures**  
4.1 | 

www.updatexp.com reserves the right to access and disclose individually identifiable information to comply with **applicable laws** and lawful government requests, to operate its systems properly or to protect itself or its users.  
  
**5.** | **How Do I Protect Your Information?**  
5.1 | 

We have strict security procedures covering the storage and disclosure of your information in order to prevent unauthorised access and to comply with the **Data Protection Act 1998**. This means that we will **ALWAYS** ask you for proof of identity before disclosing any personal information to you.  
  
**6.** | **Cookies**  
6.1 | 

A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser. On revisiting this site the computer server will recognise the cookie, giving www.updatexp.com information about your last visit. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance. If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use most of the features of our web site. [www.updatexp.com](http://www.updatexp.com/) **does not** at this point in time use cookies.

However external sites that [ www.updatexp.com](http://www.updatexp.com/) links too may be using cookies . Please refer to the site concerned for a copy of their privacy policy.  
  
  | 

**Thank You**  
www.updatexp.com 2004  
Updated - January 2004

If you have any concerns please contact **[Marc Liron](http://www.updatexp.com/contact.html)**
